<scenes region = "spaceport">
	<scene type = 'standard'>
		<name>Elyptica Spaceport's Terminal 21</name>
		<tag>terminal_21</tag>
		<summary>
			You stumble out of your shuttle into the Elyptica spaceport. It was a rough ride.
			You spent all your credits on that shuttle, you only have a small amount left.
			You should get your bearings and figure out how to get out of this joint.
		</summary>
		<ambient>You shuffle restlessly under the somewhat dim electric lights.</ambient>
		<adjacent><tag>spaceport_center</tag></adjacent>
	</scene>

	<scene type = 'standard'>
		<name>Spaceport Center</name>
		<tag>spaceport_center</tag>
		<summary>
			It wasn't very hard to find the bustling, central core of the spaceport.
			This place must be small.
			Around you are a number of shops, as well as halls to all the terminals.
		</summary>
		<ambient>The bustle makes you nervous, but the food in the shops makes you salivate.</ambient>
		<adjacent>
			<tag>terminal_21</tag>
			<tag>bathroom_1</tag>
			<tag>merc_shop</tag>
		</adjacent>
	</scene>

	<scene type = 'standard'>
		<name>The Spaceport Bathroom</name>
		<tag>bathroom_1</tag>
		<summary>
			It's remarkably well taken care of.
			You didn't think cleaning bots had gotten this advanced.
		</summary>
		<ambient>It kinda stinks in here, and you don't really have to go to the bathroom.</ambient>
		<adjacent>
			<tag>spaceport_center></tag>
		</adjacent>
	</scene>

	<scene type = 'standard'>
		<name>Cafe la Marte</name>
		<tag>cafe_1</tag>
		<summary>
			You come into a fairly quiet and spacious cafe. It's very clean and gives a relaxing atmosphere. A bored looking human barista leans behind the counter. scoping the room you see several different patrons.
At one table you see two young humans drinking coffee and well focused on their laptop screens. In a corner booth are two humans in suits talking to a zeta across from them. Lastly there is a reptillian sitting alone wearing blue MERK tech armor with five sandwitches on a large mostly empty crumb filled plate, implying there were many more at one point.
		</summary>
		<ambient>It smells like freshly baked cinnamon buns. yum!</ambient>
		<adjacent>
			<tag>spaceport_center></tag>
		</adjacent>
	</scene>

	<scene type = 'shop'>
		<name>Photon Mart</name>
		<tag>merc_shop</tag>
		<summary>Stepping inside you see vast intimidating aisles containing everything imaginable, from guass rifles to shaving cream. Thankfully there's a terminal up front with an easy to navigate catalog, as well as several drones on standby ready to aquire your purchased items for you.</summary>
		<ambient>It smells like mop water, heavily re-used mop water.</ambient>
		<adjacent>
			<tag>spaceport_center></tag>
		</adjacent>
		<market style = 'fixed'>
			<item name='old-style plasma rounds' description="They're useless on a modern gun, but deadly on an antique.">50</item>
			<item name='freeze-dried icecream' description="You thought this was a gun store, but it turns out they just have everything.">10</item>
		</market>
	</scene>

	<scene type = 'gag'>
		<name>GAG</name>
		<tag>it</tag>
		<gagtext>You hurt yourself in confusion.</gagtext>
	</scene>
</scenes>
